<ModMetaData>
	<name>Vanilla Races Expanded - Waster</name>
	<author>Oskar Potocki, Sarg Bjornson</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.4</li>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modIconPath IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">UI/VELogo</modIconPath>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/Vanilla-Expanded/VanillaExpandedFramework</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</packageId>
			<displayName>Biotech</displayName>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<packageId>vanillaracesexpanded.waster</packageId>
	<description>Vanilla Races Expanded is a brand new series of mods to enhance Biotech features, add to the storytelling and the world-building of RimWorld, and to introduce new, cool types ofxenohumans, complete with their own unique genes, behaviors, mechanics and items.

This time, we have turned our attention to Wasters. I was never a fan of how little benefit there is of having wasters in your colony, and how high maintenance they are when it comes to supplying them with yayo.

The mod brings an innovative mutation system into play, ensuring every Waster you encounter is distinctively different. Not just this, you might even stumble upon several diverse types of Wasters, each grotesquely twisted and mutated more than the last.
Waster Mod adds a new dimension to the game with brand-new structure - burn barrel, which you can use to buff your wasters through the new pollution genes, or deploy around your base to spread pollution quickly and efficiently, offering intriguing gameplay dynamics around pollution and waste. It also introduces several new genes and mutation-specific genes, expanding the scope for character development and game strategies. The system ensures no two Wasters are identical, providing a uniquely challenging experience every time.</description>
</ModMetaData>
